<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-10-23T04:36:04+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Moromis - Blog</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">California Part 3&amp;#8230; And Home?</title><link href="/2021/10/22/california-part-3/.-and-home.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="California Part 3&amp;#8230; And Home?" /><published>2021-10-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/22/california-part-3/california-part-3...-and-home</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/22/california-part-3/.-and-home.html">&lt;p&gt;In the morning I woke up and walked over to the Starbucks a couple blocks down the road. I got a bit of coffee and a breakfast sandwich, and by the time I had walked back and finished my breakfast, the shop was opening. Not long at all after the crew had pulled out all the vehicles that had been stored overnight inside the shop, they were ready to pull my van in! I was amazed at the fact that I would get priority over other customers whose vehicles had certainly been at the shop longer than my own. While the mechanics looked the old girl over to figure out the issue and why she was leaking coolant, I took a gander around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you don’t understand why I took a picture of this bus, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/YOLO_(aphorism)&quot;&gt;this might help&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/1uhXD6t.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This tree looked like a rhododendron, but had some interesting flowers
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/2xsPZkO.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were done with the work by around 1pm. The culprits had been one hose with a couple leaks and another that had been kinked, and was also the wrong type of hose (fuel line). They replaced both and I got off with what I felt was a scant cost of $180 for the whole ordeal, since insurance covered having the van towed. All-in-all way better than I expected the first breakdown to go (I do anticipate many more though).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took off towards San Francisco once more, and arrived at my friend Travis’s house in around 90 minutes. He was in a class so I talked to his mom about all sorts of topics while he was occupied. Travis had been living back at his parent’s during Covid, but usually was in LA, since he works for DreamWorks. Once Travis was done with his class, we went out for dinner, getting some Korean BBQ and catching up over yummy food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remained at the Chen’s house through Sunday and Monday. On Sunday I attended a Chinese church virtually with Mrs. Chen, and then later in the day Travis and I played some tennis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/JPQKils.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love clouds, here’s some nice formations that we saw after playing tennis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/5lXSi0C.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/1yDVT4w.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That night it was actually so stormy (rain and wind, and pretty cold too) that the power went out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/PGxX6vv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/yaBqFKu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning I worked and saw some turkeys just outside the house&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/lCUCvmW.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was on Monday after I finished work around 3pm that I decided to head home. I had visited several friends on the trip and had been gone for two weeks. I was getting homesick and there weren’t any more close friends in the area that I really wanted to visit. Also, when I looked at the map, the distance to Phoenix, AZ, where I was generally heading, was the same number of driving hours as home… It was a knife’s edge. Looking at the weather it was going to rain for the next week, and it made me realize firstly that California isn’t always sun and blue skies. It can even get pretty cold. If it’s going to be cold and rainy, I might as well be around people and places I love and know :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made the 13 hour journey straight besides one stop in the middle where I took a three hour nap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/H8zj7Rh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/rN0bUEQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Good to be back. Didn’t see colors like this in California.
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/8r5QnNN.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll keep blogging here with my adventures over the winter, but that’s the end of the California trip for now! Obviously it wasn’t the ~8 month trip I was expecting it to be, but I’m okay with that and I’m glad to be back in Washington.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In the morning I woke up and walked over to the Starbucks a couple blocks down the road. I got a bit of coffee and a breakfast sandwich, and by the time I had walked back and finished my breakfast, the shop was opening. Not long at all after the crew had pulled out all the vehicles that had been stored overnight inside the shop, they were ready to pull my van in! I was amazed at the fact that I would get priority over other customers whose vehicles had certainly been at the shop longer than my own. While the mechanics looked the old girl over to figure out the issue and why she was leaking coolant, I took a gander around.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">California Part 2</title><link href="/2021/10/19/california-part-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="California Part 2" /><published>2021-10-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/19/california-part-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/19/california-part-2.html">&lt;p&gt;I pulled over into the Dunnigan Southbound Rest Stop, halfway between Redding and San Francisco, CA. That was when I noticed that smoke was pouring from the hood of my van right in front of me. I hadn’t noticed anything wrong while driving really, but something was definitely up. I popped my hood and propped it open, but wasn’t able to get a good view with the hot smoke… or was it steam… coming up from the depths of the engine. I hopped back inside and took a look at my dials. The needle for the engine temperature was pointed all the way to the right. The van was overheating – and the question was, for how long? I hadn’t noticed at all. I hadn’t seen anything in my mirrors, and no one had signalled to me, as far as I can recall. Once the smoke finally started to clear, I checked my coolant reservoir. It was bone dry. I waited to check the radiator till the engine had cooled and it wasn’t dangerous to open the radiator cap. It looked just as deserty inside the radiator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I looked under the van and coolant was leaking down onto the ground. I crawled under and could see coolant spattered all over the hoses, engine, and underside of the van around the engine compartment. I definitely had a coolant leak. The only thing I could find from underneath though, was a strange situation with a severed (!) hose and another smaller hose that seemed to be plugged with what looked like a… golf tee?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0cWgeJp.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Huh?&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spoiler, it turned out that those hoses were not the culprit. I guess that’s an investigation for another time. Someone must really have not wanted some part of the system to work and cut it off entirely from the rest of the engine… quite the mystery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I looked the engine over, top to bottom, and couldn’t really come up with an answer. I knew I needed a shop – I didn’t even have any coolant. I had to kick myself, because I did have some coolant, but I had left it at my parents’ house in Washington State. Well, I figured, at least getting a tow wouldn’t cost me anything as the van has a good insurance policy. So I called up the insurance and lodged a request for a tow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then I waited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the next three hours. Turns out, when I finally got a response from the insurance company, they had called 50 tow companies in the area and none had availability. I had lodged some calls myself, and was waiting on a response from one in the town I was hoping to get a tow to, Woodland, CA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, I read a book, ate some dinner, and snapped some photos of a terribly good-looking lizard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/9PMHEd8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lizzy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I got a call back from the tow company that I had rung up several hours earlier. The man on the phone, Michael, told me he hoped he might have availability now. He made sure someone could come out with a tow truck capable of hauling my van, and then gave me an estimate for the tow – which I would pay for out-of-pocket, and then submit to insurance later. He asked me to pull up the text he had sent to my number and fill out the details of my situation. When I went to my texts though, I only saw one, and it was from my insurance. They had finally located a tow company and they were on the way! After an over three hour wait, I suddenly had two tow trucks ready to come pick up my van. I got back on the phone with Michael, and apologized and told him that my insurance had finally come through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two hours later, the tow truck arrived. It was well and dark by then, but we got the van loaded up. It was really quite the sight to see my big old van on top of a similarly large tow truck’s flatbed, all said towering a good 13+ feet in the air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/l9vApzG.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a long afternoon, we drove the van down to Woodland and unloaded the van in front of the shop. Originally, I had wanted it towed to one shop, Alves. However, the tow truck operator, Eddie, told me that it wouldn’t get looked at the next day, a Saturday, if I took it there. He suggested a different shop, F &amp;amp; R, telling me that he took all of his own vehicles there, and even had his son’s truck in at the moment. I figured he probably had a connection with the shop, but if he was telling the truth I figured there was no harm in taking it there, and the worst that could happen would be a great story. Eddie unloaded my van in front of the shop and had me re-park it into an empty spot, after which he left and I went to bed, hoping that the next morning the repair would be an easy one and I could keep driving at some point on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;cliffhanger&quot;&gt;To be continued!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I pulled over into the Dunnigan Southbound Rest Stop, halfway between Redding and San Francisco, CA. That was when I noticed that smoke was pouring from the hood of my van right in front of me. I hadn’t noticed anything wrong while driving really, but something was definitely up. I popped my hood and propped it open, but wasn’t able to get a good view with the hot smoke… or was it steam… coming up from the depths of the engine. I hopped back inside and took a look at my dials. The needle for the engine temperature was pointed all the way to the right. The van was overheating – and the question was, for how long? I hadn’t noticed at all. I hadn’t seen anything in my mirrors, and no one had signalled to me, as far as I can recall. Once the smoke finally started to clear, I checked my coolant reservoir. It was bone dry. I waited to check the radiator till the engine had cooled and it wasn’t dangerous to open the radiator cap. It looked just as deserty inside the radiator.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Train Mountain And California Beginnings</title><link href="/2021/10/17/train-mountain-and-california-beginnings.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Train Mountain And California Beginnings" /><published>2021-10-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/17/train-mountain-and-california-beginnings</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/17/train-mountain-and-california-beginnings.html">&lt;p&gt;After leaving the Deschutes National Forest midday on Sunday, I drove down to Chiloquin, OR, a small town north of Klamath Falls. Just outside of Chiloquin proper there’s a large plot of land (over 2000 acres) on which sits Train Mountain. Train Mountain is dominated by a central hub from which stems many miles of 7 1/2” (1/8 scale) train track. The scale of the trains is such that you can sit on the train cars/caboose and drive around on the track.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Uncle David (of the Savage line) lives and works at Train Mountain, giving tours by driving an electric engine pulling two or more “cars” with four seats each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Uncle David and I
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/fztabL6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I was at Train Mountain, we went to The Potbelly Cafe, a delightfully warm (in both senses of the word) dinery where many of the locals and Train Mountain volunteers and attendees gather. The food is good and the coffee is hot. The easy conversation was a reminder of small towns and their draw for me personally – a place where everyone knows everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Train Mountain I quickly found the local denizens and tried to secure their love…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Charlie, the hunter
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/d1nI400.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Maggie, the house cat
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/aOAzZwE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went on one of David’s tours on the second day I was there&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/UfJ4xBQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/fbgPlmx.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Remember, this is 1/8th scale – pretty amazing detail right?
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/sl2knqx.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a wonderful two days at Train Mountain (though cold, 20 degrees or colder in the morning) I got back on the road, headed towards Redding, CA, and then San Francisco to visit friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fueled up soon after I left and also got some groceries at the fuel station shop – including a tasty treat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Those of you who know me well know that Umpqua is my favorite ice cream
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/GfdfRDS.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The afternoon of leaving Chiloquin I went past Mount Shasta&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/YYVfW6x.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and made a hard right to go to Montague, CA. I planned to do a ~65 mile ride there, following the route of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gravelhugger.com/&quot;&gt;Shasta Gravel Hugger Half&lt;/a&gt;. I parked and slept next to the city park and the next day started off on the route. It was so cold, windy, and at times even raining a little, that I quit about 17 miles in, looping back for a total of just under 30 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s some pictures from the ride:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/j4dito9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/NrxabNu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0BvY1yZ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here’s the route:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;iframe height=&quot;405&quot; width=&quot;590&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://www.strava.com/activities/6107774853/embed/822ea24c5dd81e3a1d4c058aea384052b7206810&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 20px;&quot;&gt;(Additionally, here’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gravelhugger.com/seriespage&quot;&gt;the routes on the official webpage&lt;/a&gt;, to see the whole route that I was going to do)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cold weather told me I needed to go further south and find the sun once more.
I drove to and through Redding, and ended up a bit south of the main town at the California Visitor Center. I stayed for a couple nights at the Wal-Mart, stocking up on some much needed groceries, and working during the day at The Bean, a nice coffee shop (with wifi, the quintessential need). The weather was perfect. I woke up to 50 degrees and it would climb to 70 or perhaps 80 during the day. A nice breeze kept everything cool though, and I wore a jacket for most of the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of entertainment I’ve been reading Searching for God Knows What by Donald Miller, and while I was sat in the Wal-Mart parking lot I watched through the first season of Alice in Borderland – I would highly recommend if you liked Squid Game (especially the beginning). I’ve also been reading Exodus, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=Isaiah%2055&amp;amp;version=NIV&quot;&gt;Isaiah 55&lt;/a&gt;, and re-reading John.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the mornings I treated myself to a couple of nice breakfasts, including Fruit Loops&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/d110Lho.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and French toast&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/i2W7xpc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/aBKS6w0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I even went into the store and got some maple syrup, which I sorely missed when I made pancakes the week prior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On another random food note, turns out you can get Noosa yoghurt in large containers. Wow!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/a9vXd5t.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After spending a few days adjusting to California, I headed towards San Francisco, a 3 hour drive away. But about halfway there, disaster struck…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;cliffhanger&quot;&gt;To be continued!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">After leaving the Deschutes National Forest midday on Sunday, I drove down to Chiloquin, OR, a small town north of Klamath Falls. Just outside of Chiloquin proper there’s a large plot of land (over 2000 acres) on which sits Train Mountain. Train Mountain is dominated by a central hub from which stems many miles of 7 1/2” (1/8 scale) train track. The scale of the trains is such that you can sit on the train cars/caboose and drive around on the track.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Deschutes National Forest</title><link href="/2021/10/16/deschutes-national-forest.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deschutes National Forest" /><published>2021-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/16/deschutes-national-forest</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/16/deschutes-national-forest.html">&lt;p&gt;Thursday night, after driving from Smith Rock State Park, I found a spot tucked away in the town of Sisters, OR. For those of you familiar with it, this had the feel of Leavenworth, WA, or maybe even more appropriately Jackson Hole, WY. A bit of a tourist town and touting the Wild West, the town did not lack for parking spots – perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday morning, I looked up the closest independently-owned coffee shop with wifi and a spot to sit, headed over, and settled in for the last bit of work for the week. After a leisurely six hours, and a very successful refactoring of our tabular data display, I packed up and headed off to the Indian Ford campground, just south of Black Butte, in the Deschutes National Forest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My chosen spot, not very far off the road, which itself wasn’t too far from the highway. I was able to very easily drive over to the campground and use their toilet though.
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/NzEpQku.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My plan was to boondock for the weekend and enjoy some gravel biking before heading farther south. I cooked up some beef stew with fresh onions and bell pepper for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/bdirQ8r.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With some pears-in-a-can for my cooking snack&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/qWe607P.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time it was all cooked up, the beef stew didn’t look too shabby, despite it coming from a bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/bINHGYs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I remembered I have a stack of crossword puzzles so I finished one off during and after dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/yf2hij0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first morning (Saturday) I took my time in the morning and cooked up eggs (with some more of the onion and bell pepper from the previous night), sausage and toast, washed down with a nice pot of French press coffee. Can you tell I like food? Sometimes it’s the most interesting part of my day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/fsDdwyC.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I was worried I would miss toast… And I did. It turns out you can make toast just fine with some butter and a frying pan though!
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/IMe02u5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After my brunch, I set off on a ~37 mile loop, with about 8 miles extra to get to and from the start of the loop. I’ll put some pictures here from my ride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A view looking south across the Indian Ford Meadow Preserve of what I’d assume is South Sister and Mt Bachelor
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/kYi8R2H.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The road was either bouldery, washboardy, or sandy as in this picture, inside a recently-burned portion of forest
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/gEnIngs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ajwd7at.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At one point the road deteriorated into an unrideable, barely recognizable double track
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/wKYup9o.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The second half of the loop was filled with tracks that would be treacherous on a mountain bike, much less the 37mm tires I was running. The views were constantly changing and kept me going (and the knowledge that I would be able to sit down and be done at some point hehe).
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/g8n6ZR6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Finally seeing pavement after some 3 hours of rock and dirt…
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/7oWTzDC.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The trust steed after a solid day of riding
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/43BH0rA.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the end of a day, with another sunset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Tp2NQ2E.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here’s the Strava for the ride&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;iframe height=&quot;405&quot; width=&quot;590&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://www.strava.com/activities/6089393526/embed/304fa219dba30352d8f2071c55e63f245629ad34&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Thursday night, after driving from Smith Rock State Park, I found a spot tucked away in the town of Sisters, OR. For those of you familiar with it, this had the feel of Leavenworth, WA, or maybe even more appropriately Jackson Hole, WY. A bit of a tourist town and touting the Wild West, the town did not lack for parking spots – perfect.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Smith Rocks Day 2</title><link href="/2021/10/13/smith-rocks-day-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Smith Rocks Day 2" /><published>2021-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/13/smith-rocks-day-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/13/smith-rocks-day-2.html">&lt;p&gt;The second day at Smith Rocks I woke up early, around 6, and got to the park right around 7, when it opened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here’s the view on the drive over:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ptCZV7W.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sunrise&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I purchased my day pass and set up in the outer lot, with a great view of the cliffs. I was the first one there, and so I was able to use the freshly cleaned porta potty and pick the best spot in the parking lot, which for me was a spot with a no parking spot on the passenger side, so I can swing my doors open and cook and work outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here’s the view right when I got there:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/z6WCvYz.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The spot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got set up, went out along the rim trail and got some photos of the sunrise on the rocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/rY3MHLO.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/SBef6Bf.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a couple paraglider zipping around the canyon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/PXOY4xr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then a hot air ballon appeared, there’s a paraglider above the balloon in this photo:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/OcoTSzw.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made some oatmeal and coffee for breakfast. I took some photos to show you some of my process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My sink for washing dishes&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HFmeCUL.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My drying rack
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/KQ3pmeC.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After breakfast I got to work. But today it was special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My workplace
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Pta0mx7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The view from my workplace
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/jmAGoGG.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;And as always, my motto&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/zaB8NUw.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After work I went bouldering and took absolutely no pictures of it… I also didn’t have any real guide, since I didn’t want to spend forty dollars for the guidebook when I would only be there a short while. I did look up a text guide to some of the boulders and worked out where one was that had some relatively easy problems on it. I am weak from not climbing in a long time, and that being added to my still raw ring finger (electric drill incident for those of you not in the know) and aloneness, I didn’t top out on anything. I didn’t really even get more than four feet off the ground. But I climbed till the sun went down over the canyon wall and the valley began to get cold, a breeze running through it. Then I hiked back out and set off towards Sisters, Oregon, with the goal of doing some biking in the Deschutes National Forest.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The second day at Smith Rocks I woke up early, around 6, and got to the park right around 7, when it opened.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Train Mountain Stars</title><link href="/2021/10/11/train-mountain-stars.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Train Mountain Stars" /><published>2021-10-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/11/train-mountain-stars</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/11/train-mountain-stars.html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/jMALYCv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Smith Rocks Day 1</title><link href="/2021/10/10/smith-rocks-day-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Smith Rocks Day 1" /><published>2021-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/10/smith-rocks-day-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/10/smith-rocks-day-1.html">&lt;p&gt;Alright, so those of you that waited for the cliffhanger ending… I did not run out of gas. But I sure did pay through the nose!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I woke up and for the first time on my trip had to scrape ice off my windshield (from the inside, there’s downsides to sleeping in your vehicle and condensation is one), then got driving. I ended up in Shaniko within 10 minutes of driving, and they had gas, ending my almost 100 mile drought. They only charged $5.99 per gallon too! What a steal! I begrudgingly purchased 5 gallons and kept driving. I stopped only a bit longer down the road at the Cow Canyon rest stop and worked for a while. Boy it was cold. Hard to keep your fingers typing when it’s below freezing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After lunch I trucked the last hour or so down to Smith Rocks State Park. Here’s the first [safe-to-take-a-picture-of] view:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/MvqQuRa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then once you’re in the park… the real view:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/DNHUaVE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(thanks Google for stitching me a nice panorama)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I figured on doing some rock climbing, but once I got there – I realized I had no idea where to start. I got my parking pass for the day and took a gander at the map&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/JB0iuy0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;It's a map, it's a map, it's a map&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ended up just hiking for the first day, down into the valley (canyon?) and all the way around clockwise to the East, crossing the Crooked River at the Horse Ford. I talked to several groups of climbers and asked about the grades of what they were climbing. There’s some really interesting stuff, a lot of it sandstone. I didn’t get any pictures of the routes as I was too busy talking to people about them. I hiked up one cliff wall to look at all the climbs along it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I went up&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/63MQKh9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;And up&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/3SGf0so.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;And up&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/LJ7H0hz.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The view from the very top:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/rIZBhjw.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The butte across the river is the level of the Smith Rocks visitor center and parking lots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Going down was a bit sketchy in flip flops so barefoot felt much safer&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HnQpcKl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After my adventure it was getting late, so I talked to a couple of other guys in vans about the local spots to park for the night. They told me that some people pay for tent camping and then stay in their vans, and others drive up the road 10 minutes to a rest area and park there. I chose the latter, and it turned out to be half a rest area and half a state park, with a cool bridge and some mighty tall cliffs. It’s called the Peter Skene Ogden State Park/Rest Area in case you want to visit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Look at that rock formation!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/biAyIa2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Another view&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/BvHwzLh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Close up” of the rock&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/8nzUQij.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you want to see larger versions and more photos (even photos of my food…), here’s an album:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://photos.app.goo.gl/NCL47tkqwZ6v7wQS6&quot;&gt;Smith Rocks State Park Day 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Alright, so those of you that waited for the cliffhanger ending… I did not run out of gas. But I sure did pay through the nose!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Leaving Tieton And Highway 97</title><link href="/2021/10/08/leaving-tieton-and-highway-97.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Leaving Tieton And Highway 97" /><published>2021-10-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/08/leaving-tieton-and-highway-97</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/08/leaving-tieton-and-highway-97.html">&lt;p&gt;On the fifth I worked till 1pm or so at the Claussen’s, and Beth made me breakfast and lunch. Then, just before I left, she baked chocolate chip cookies and gave me a bunch. I’m a sucker for food so I’ll definitely be stopping by on my way back to Washington 😊&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/SRSSSgl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cookies!!!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down from Tieton into Naches I went, and then from Highway 12 to Highway 97, which I’ll be taking all the way to Klamath Falls, where I’ll be visiting my Uncle David. I drove for a couple hours and stopped on the Columbia River at Maryhill State Park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/4JuZy5C.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Maryhill State Park, looking East down the Columbia&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There, I waded a bit in the water and had dinner – a burrito crisped on my stove and cookies. After eating and brushing my teeth, I started South once more (almost immediately entering Oregon, since the border is halfway over the Columbia). Soon after crossing the river, there was a sign: “Next Gas 94 Miles.” I had about a quarter of my front tank and a full (or so I thought) rear tank. That’s enough to make it… right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A quick break since I’ve been calculating my MPG since I headed out from the Seattle area. Let me tell you, it’s not pretty. As in 7 miles per gallon ugly. Oh well, I love and hate the old girl in equal measure. I wouldn’t have it any other way – I’m not trying to live the “van life” or experience great comfort in my travels. That’s no fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, so knowing that I get 7 MPG (I didn’t really know that then, I would have guessed at least 8), and the front tank holding 22 gallons and the rear holding 13 (?)… I’ll let you do the math because I’m too lazy. Anyways, it was all too soon that I found my front tank empty, and then my rear tank sure did go down fast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then again, I know that. The rear leaks into the front because the valve that controls which tank the engine draws from and returns to works for the former but not the latter. So it goes down quick and then I switch back to the front and use whatever is in there. Sometimes I empty the front, use the rear, and when I fill up the next time the front only takes 5 gallons or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/TWNAyxK.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lonely driving on Highway 97&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then… I stopped on the side of the road cause I was sleepy, watched the rest of Squid Game (meh ending), and bedded down for the night. Though I don’t have my father’s gift for sleep, cars and semis can’t keep me awake even when they’re passing by all night right next to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;cliffhanger&quot;&gt;Guess we'll find out if I made it, or how close I got before I ran out of gas, next time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">On the fifth I worked till 1pm or so at the Claussen’s, and Beth made me breakfast and lunch. Then, just before I left, she baked chocolate chip cookies and gave me a bunch. I’m a sucker for food so I’ll definitely be stopping by on my way back to Washington 😊</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Driving From Monroe To Tieton</title><link href="/2021/10/04/driving-from-monroe-to-tieton.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Driving From Monroe To Tieton" /><published>2021-10-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/04/driving-from-monroe-to-tieton</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/04/driving-from-monroe-to-tieton.html">&lt;p&gt;I drove from rainy, foggy Monroe WA the other day (October 3rd) over Snoqualmie Pass on I-90. I pulled over at a rest stop (Indian John) to use the restroom and felt tired, so I slept an hour. I woke up around 7 and decided to just stay overnight in the rest area parking lot. I ate some of the pizza I made (see the photo in the last post!), watched an episode of Squid Game, and went to bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day (October 4th), I woke up and drove a bit down the road to a local coffee shop, got some coffee and a breakfast sandwich, and worked till just before noon. While I was there one of the workers sliced off the tip of their finger with a mandolin while cutting onions 😬 I passed on some insights from my recent drill-related injury. They won’t have a fun time the first time they take off the bandage, hopefully they figure out how to get it off without it sticking/hurting too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After work I drove to Tieton (pronounced Tie-eh-tawn), northwest of Yakima. I met up with some friends of the family, the Claussens. Phil was the only one home and he’s got a bad cold, so I didn’t talk to him for too long, but caught him up on what I and my siblings have been up to. I then went for a bike ride through the hills to the east of Tieton. The paved roads quickly give way to gravel on most routes out of town, and then after crossing and passing a couple gates, the gravel increased to the size of my head. It was quite the adventure, and it was a hot slog to the top of the mountain. Once I was on the ridgeline there was a nice breeze though, and I picked my way to the other end, where the comically large gravel finally started to subside. From there there was a beautiful descent with gorgeous views of Tieton River. I made my way all the way down to Highway 12 at Windy Point. The route I was following kept going, following the river farther east before heading back into the hills and looping back north and ending about halfway back to the 410-12 junction. It was about 4 at that point though and I was worried about it getting dark. I hadn’t brought any lights. I rode 12 north then east, and then south and west back into Tieton. There’s a pretty good climb from Naches up towards Tieton and a couple other rolling hills coming into town, and overall I was tuckered by the time I got back. Having not been on a bike in… months? – 30+ miles was biting off a bit more than I could chew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here’s the ride:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;iframe height=&quot;405&quot; width=&quot;590&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://www.strava.com/activities/6064986504/embed/3a28e445d1fa57560db5498f53bb144520b934c0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll leave you with some pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Sunrise&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/FdUfU8E.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;sunrise!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Getting over an elk fence with a bike…&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Ix25h7V.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The terrain I was riding&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/4RHgHET.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Tieton river (from far away)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/SilVasd.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Tieton river (close up) 1&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ZmDD2Lm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Tieton river (close up) 2&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/UyGOV5Q.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Kitty cat&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ChZcWB1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;kitty!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I drove from rainy, foggy Monroe WA the other day (October 3rd) over Snoqualmie Pass on I-90. I pulled over at a rest stop (Indian John) to use the restroom and felt tired, so I slept an hour. I woke up around 7 and decided to just stay overnight in the rest area parking lot. I ate some of the pizza I made (see the photo in the last post!), watched an episode of Squid Game, and went to bed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pizza</title><link href="/2021/10/03/pizza.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pizza" /><published>2021-10-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/10/03/pizza</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/10/03/pizza.html">&lt;p&gt;I didn’t actually cook this today. But I did make it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was delicious&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/daD6B41.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pizza&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I didn’t actually cook this today. But I did make it!</summary></entry></feed>